{
    "id": "3e7344c5f4014ff5b68b12e5de276775",
    "title": "Errors in the use of nouns and verbs: exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "09c356fb2b834d99976e0c147b52d628",
            "title": "Errors In Nouns And Verbs",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Be careful not to .................................. your money.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lose",
                        "loose"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have they ................................... this box?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "weighed",
                        "weighted"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mathematics ....................................... not easy to learn.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You have to learn this ...................................... by heart.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "poem",
                        "poetry"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "When she entered her room, she saw her books lying on the ..............................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "floor",
                        "ground"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Which is the ............................................. to the railway station?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "road",
                        "street"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Are you .......................................... in this program?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "interesting",
                        "interested"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She sometimes ...................................... purple shoes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "wears",
                        "puts on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "There .................................. a lot of apples on the tree.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "are"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "What ........................................... eat?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "do cows",
                        "cows"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}